jcink.net 2017-11-16

# Jcink.com Forum Hosting

**Jcink.com Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to Jcink.com. We have limited the amount and types of personal information that we need from you. We wish for you to be fully informed of how your information is gathered and used. This is the privacy policy for "jcink.com" Please see [here](http://jcink.com/?p=legal) for all of our service(s) individual privacy policies. 

**What information does Jcink.com gather & How we use the information:**

Jcink.com gathers the IP address information, GET query, and date time of request, in server logs in order to aid us in traffic statistics, within its own site and server-wide. You may elect to block the HTTP_REFERER from being passed to our website in your browser or via a third party program. By using Jcink.com you also agree to the [Jcink Forum Boards](http://jfb.jcink.com/?p=privacy) privacy policy because we use this service for our forums (forums.jcink.com) 

**Cookies:**

Cookies are used to better your experience. You can disable cookies if you wish using browser settings or any other program. However, this could affect your ability to use features such as logging in to our site. Our advertisement providers can also use cookies for tracking purposes, and display ads. 

**Third Party Advertisements**

Jcink Forum Boards uses third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site and hosted boards. These companies may collect and use information about your visits to Jcink Forum Boards as well as other web sites.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.   
If you would like more information please visit the following links:
